

PROFILE

Student of Computer Engineering. Responsible and perseverant person. Good skills solving tasks using communication and time management.

I am looking for new experiences to expand my development skills.

INFORMATION



09/03/2000

in Matías Gines

Matias Gines

Matiasgines47@gmail.com

LANGUAGES

English A.2 -Oral -Written

HOBBIES

Cycling Photography Literature

SOFT SKILLS

Teamwork. Organization. Ability to adapt. Proactive.

MATIAS GINES

EDUCATION

National University of La Plata

08/02/2021 - Present.

Studying Computer Engineering.

Prefectura Naval Argentina.

07/02/2020 -18/09/2021.

Degree in maritime safety.

Studies not completed. Highlighted by good conduct and academic performance.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Benefit You. – Call center.

01/08/2021 -07/02/2022.

Sales of financial products.

Arcos Dorados. Mc Donald's.

27/11/2017 - 05/01/2020

Customer service and cash register. Trained in sales and labor productivity.

Living del Sur. - Sales and customer service

13/03/2017 - 06/11/2017

showroom sales and community manager

COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

JPMorgan-Fundación Pescar.

01/12/2021 - Present.

Full stack web developer (bootcamp):

-Development of interpersonal competences: 128 hs

-Programming IT Education (full stack MERN): 172 hs

SKILLS

Bootstrap

CSS3

Git/Github

HTML5

Javascript













PERFIL

Estudiante de Ing. En computación. Me considero una persona responsable y perseverante. Con buena actitud al momento de resolver tareas, utilizando la comunicación y gestión del tiempo. Estoy en búsqueda de nuevas experiencias para expandir mis habilidades en programación.

INFORMACIÓN

1154821319



09/03/2000



in Matías Gines



Matias Gines



Matiasgines47@gmail.com

IDIOMAS

Inglés A.2 -Oral -Escrito

AFICIONES

Ciclismo. Fotografía. Literatura.

APTITUDES

Trabajo en equipo. Organización. Capacidad de adaptación. Proactivo.

MATIAS GINES

EDUCACIÓN

Universidad Nacional de La Plata

08/02/2021 - Actualidad.

Cursando Ing. En computación.

Escuela de Oficiales de la Prefectura Naval Argentina.

07/02/2020 -18/09/2021.

Licenciatura en seguridad marítima.

Estudios no completados, destacado por buena conducta y desempeño académico.

EXPERIENCIA LABORAL

Benefit You. – Call center.

01/08/2021 -07/02/2022.

Venta de productos financieros.

Arcos Dorados. Mcdonald's.

27/11/2017 - 05/01/2020

Atención al cliente y caja.

Capacitado en ventas y productividad laboral.

Living del Sur. - Sales and customer service

13/03/2017 - 06/11/2017

Encargado de realizar ventas en showroom y mediante marketing digital.

CURSOS Y CERTIFICACIONES

JPMorgan-Fundación Pescar.

01/12/2021 - Actualidad

Programación web full stack (bootcamp):

- -Desarrollo de competencias interpersonales: 128 hs
- -Programación Educación IT (full stack MERN) 172 hs

HABILIDADES

Bootstrap CSS3 Git/github HTML5 **Javascript**









